<?xml version = "1.0" encoding = "UTF-8" ?>
<Computer id="jmail" name="HexMail.com" ip="74.125.237.119" security="5">
  <admin type="basic"/>

  <account username="#PLAYERNAME#" password="rosered" type="2"/>
  <account username="Crymz0n" password="blackhawk" type="2"/>
  <account username="coolclyde36" password="splinter1" type="2"/>
  <account username="r0byn132" password="mistletoe" type="2"/>
  <account username="TMichael" password="lickitysplit" type="2"/>

  <!-- Localizer note!
  Never translate the "sender" or "recipient" fields. In cases where something mentions a password
  (like below) make extra sure to leave the password in English, both where it's mentioned and where it's used.
  -->
  
  <mailServer name="HexMail" color="255,141,48">

    <email recipient="coolclyde36" sender="r0byn132@hexmail.com" subject="RTSPSmasher">

I've finished compiling the latest version of RTSPSmasher. Login to this IP with the credentials I gave you.

IP Address: 192.154.1.241

-Robyn

</email>

	<email recipient="TMichael" sender="OfficialPsylance@psymail.com" subject="Start Of Investigation">

	In reply to your request (and in accordance with our ToS) we will shortly begin an investigation into the recent breach into your personal home system.
	
	Please be assured that we will work tirelessly to catch the person responsible and to ensure that you will get the justice you want.
	
	Thank you for your incredible devotion to the company.
	
	Yours Faithfully - D. Phelps (Head of the Psylance Internal Investigations Division)
	
	(P.S: Please ensure you are signed up to our company mail service to ensure more efficient and secure transit of mail between staff members. Thanks)
	(P.P.S: The server itself can be found here: #PSYMAIL_IP#)
	(P.P.P.S: Please do not download a copy of this email as distribution could be disastrous for the company)

	</email>

	<email recipient="TMichael" sender="OfficialPsylance@psymail.com" subject="Investigation Status">

	I am pleased to inform you that an investigation is underway about the attack on your personal computer. We have yet to catch the hacker responsible, however the trail is strong.
  
  In the meantime, we hope that the compensation you have received is enough to get you back on your feet after this terrible incident.
  
  Thanks for placing your faith in Psylance's hands and I hope to see you around the offices again soon.
  
  Yours faithfully - D. Phelps (Head of the Psylance Internal Investigations Division)

	</email>

  </mailServer>

</Computer>