<?xml version = "1.0" encoding = "UTF-8" ?>
<Computer id="dPsyInternal" name="Psylance Internal Services" security="4" type="empty" ip="#PSYINTERNAL_IP#" icon="Psylance">

  <portsForCrack val="5" />
  <ports>21, 22, 25, 443, 80, 1433</ports>
  <firewall level="-1"/>
  <proxy time="1" />
  <trace time="120" />
  <portRemap>22=340</portRemap>
  <dlink target="dPsyArchives" />
  
  <file path="home" name="Organization.txt">Because of the way I've set up our automatic archiving system, please use the root folder "projects" for all reports and files - some programs etc generate junk in the home directory that I want to avoid piling in with our actual work, so I'm keeping this blank.
Thanks!
-Faith
  </file>

  <encryptedFile path="projects/investigations" name="Employee_Breach_Incident.dec" header="Psylance cyber security internal investigations division inc.">
Psylance Cyber Security - internal investigations division.
---------------------------------------

Psylance security employee Tom Michaels experienced a heavy attack on his personal work computer.
Upon thorough inspection of the computer system, it appears that many personal items of Michaels' were stolen and/or deleted - including bank details, personal photos, work documents and several more vital files.

After more investigation took place, a discovery was made. The logs folder of the system in question was completely empty, which was surprising given that Michaels had been using the system moments before the incident.
This obviously leads us to assume that the attack was performed remotely where the logs folder was wiped after the attack.

To further the investigation, we have forensics agents creating memory dumps, where they will be able to analyse the lost logs and inevitably find the culprit.

Psylance is committed to the security of their employees, and will be ensuring that the victim of these attacks is compensated.
  </encryptedFile>

  <file path="projects/investigations" name="WhitelistGlitches.zip">#BINARY#</file>

  <file path="projects/misc" name="IRC_Config.txt">//IRC Baseline setup for roaming admins - copy over to new client accounts for easy maintenance
Color=67,204,148 //PSYLANCE GREEN
//CORE USER SET
:user name="faithless" color="0,209,232"
:user name="dardypants" color="202,98,0"
:user name="da_vito" color="0,196,82"
//Admin Config
:Auth public="false" sec="restricted"
  </file>

  <file path="projects/misc" name="IRC_setup.zip">#BINARY#</file>

</Computer>