<?xml version = "1.0" encoding = "UTF-8" ?>
<Computer id="sidOblivionMail" name="Oblivion Digital Mail Server" icon="DLCServer" type="3">

<dlink target="sidOblivionMain"/>

<portsForCrack val="5" />
<ports>25, 22, 21, 80</ports>
<firewall level="50" solution="PSUCTVEGNVVAIUBBJHVOADUIAFVBHEAAF7Y3KJE3QI8HS8HE8R4"/>

<account username="davet_84" password="bigprofitsbigfun" type="2"/>
<account username="paulm_99" password="ictisinsane" type="2"/>
<account username="robbyg_94" password="hatsarefun" type="2"/>
<account username="jacobp_64" password="snitchesgetstiches" type="2"/>
<account username="hannahv_82" password="snitchesgetstiches" type="2"/>

<file path="home" name="IMPORTANT.txt">Files are not to be stored on the mail server. If you need something to be stored, it either goes onto the mainframe or doesn't go anywhere.
Thanks - Paul</file>

<mailServer name="Oblivion Digital" color="176,94,224">

    <email recipient="paulm_99" sender="davet_84@O.DCompanyMail.com" subject="Technical Difficulties">

		My computer has started to really slow down recently. I have no idea why that is but I'll need you to come and fix it at some point today.

		I've also received a metric-s**t ton of spam mail. I have no time to clear it out so I'll need you to log into my mail account and do something about it. The password is "bigprofitsbigfun".

		Now hurry up, we've got money to make!

		-David Triston, Lead Developer of Oblivion Digital

	</email>
	
    <email recipient="paulm_99" sender="robbyg_94@O.DCompanyMail.com" subject="Party">
	
		Hey Paul, we're planning a little party for the entire staff team after work. I wanted to know if you wanted to join? Don't worry, David doesn't know about our plans, the damn fool only cares about one thing and that's profits...
	
		After the uproar from our latest game I'm surprised that we're still in business, atleast David's got one talent he's good at: persuading our fans that our underdeveloped game is something to hype over.
	
		Anyway, enough rambling. Hit me up after work and I'll let the guys know that your coming.
	
		-Robby
	
	</email>
	
	<email recipient="davet_84" sender="paulm_99@O.DCompanyMail.com" subject="Slow PC Issue Solved">
	
		This is just a quick e-mail telling you what I've done to fix the problems you've been experiencing.
	
		It turns out that a hacker managed to get a hold of your IP address and was using that to cause issues for your system. Luckily enough I managed to change the IP address before the hacker could do any serious damage to your PC.
		
		Incase you ever need it, your new IP address is: 184.253.4.19
	
		I'm working on clearing your e-mail account now. If there's any more problems, tell me via e-mail and I'll take a look.
	
		-Paul McMellan, IT Technician
	
	</email>

  </mailServer>
  
</Computer>